We're in Brazil, baby.
>> [music]
>> The sunset is insane here.
>> Botequim casual.
Hello everyone. Welcome back to my
channel. Another day, another vlog. Your
girl is headed to Drumroll, please.
It's my first time flying first class. I
flew up before once, but only because I
got upgraded, but this is my first time
like actually getting it for myself. The
real ones know I never grew up with that
type of experience. I'm just so excited.
Can you tell I'm out of breath?
Cuz I'm just that excited.
>> [music]
[music]
>> I'm out here drinking wine. Who doesn't
like wine? New York to Brazil.
Nice little socks, little toothbrush,
toothpaste.
Here's my cream
and
>> [music]
>> Good morning everyone. I just woke up.
Apparently I look all crazy. Brush my
teeth.
Guys, anyone that knows me knows that on
flight I get so much anxiety, so [music]
I never sleep well on flight. This is
the first flight ever where I actually
slept good. I feel great.
>> [music]
>> We're about to be in Brazil soon.
My girls are waiting for me. I'm so
excited to see them. They landed before
me. They said that they're here at the
duty-free shop, but I don't see them.
Hello. Guys, I see them.
I'm going to try to surprise them.
>> [laughter]
>> When all your friends have different
aesthetics She's the classic y'all.
She's the classic y'all. Ashley sure and
then we got
clothing brand owner Alchemist. Let's
go.
Let's wear You look like you're going
camping, my.
>> [laughter]
>> Yeah. Not the hiking shoes.
Shop, guys.
>> [music]
[music]
>> Okay, guys. We just made it to the
Airbnb.
I'm excited. The elevator is through
this door right here. We're still
waiting for the other two girls because
the elevator was literally the size of
Stop. This is our new home, guys. Airbnb
tour. Pretty ass [music] fridge. I love
pretty fridges. Wow.
Guys.
Oh my god.
Is that a barbecue? Shut up, my Airbnb.
[music]
We are walking in Copacabana.
Copacabana beach. It's so hot. I'm a
little overstimulated, but it's so much
fun. There's so many people. It is New
Year's Eve right now, so it is insane
[music] here. Like there's so many
people. It's packed. Yeah, everyone's
wearing their little bikinis [music] and
stuff.
In Brazil, they have this tradition
where they do fireworks on New Year's
Eve and then they Everybody wears white,
so we got our little white outfits.
It's giving cottagecore. It's giving
princess. Thank you. Where's your prom?
My prom White Fox.
>> [laughter]
>> Yes, I've only been in Brazil for less
than 1 day and I can already tell you
that I love it. The vibes [music]
amazing. People gorgeous. Food so far
has been amazing. I didn't vlog it, but
we sat with like this random Brazilian
woman who was so nice to us. Enter
picture here. Oh, we took a picture with
her.
She was so sweet. So, fun fact the
restaurant was like there was no space
for us when [music] we walked in, but we
were so hungry. And that woman was
sitting at a table alone and she offered
us to sit with her. We don't speak a
lick of Portuguese. She don't really
speak a lick of English, so we were kind
of just like smiling and nodding.
We took selfies together. Yeah, she was
the sweetest lady. We took a selfie with
her.
>> I think she was low-key regretting her
decision for a second.
She was trying to eat her food and we're
like, "Where are you from?"
Here's the finished [music] look.
We are ready for New Year's in Brazil.
>> [music]
>> Feliz ano novo.
Guys, look how beautiful it is in
Brazil. Like oh my goodness. There are
[music] so many people here. Like it's
actually insane. We got the whole crew
plus Bruno. This is our boy Bruno.
[music] He's security guarding us. Yes,
Bruno.
Let's go.
Just one.
We're waiting for midnight because it's
going to be New Year's Day and that's
when all the fireworks are going to go.
I'm like so shook at how gorgeous it is.
Look how unreal it is right now.
My crazy friends.
Hola.
>> [music]
>> Good.
Wow. Okay, [music] Lena, Lena, Lena,
Lena.
Oh.
She's messy. She's messy.
>> [music]
>> Oh, [music]
we look a mess. We wish you a healthy
and happy 2020. We look like we went
through a war. That was an insane
experience. I lost one shoe and then I
was able to take another one that
[music] I found. We wish you a happy New
Year.
Your girl's currently rushing, hawk girl
walking cuz I'm meeting my girls Talia
and Ariel for brunch. Not going to lie,
your girl slept in a little bit too
long. Your girl is tired.
>> [music]
[music]
>> I look and feel like a gremlin right
now. I sound like one, too. My girl
Ashley is back there
rotting on the couch.
Yesterday we went out and we went out
till 5:00 a.m. And you guys know I don't
really go out like that. So, when I do,
it's the time. And I lost my voice,
missing a nail.
I got white stuff on my chin. This is
pimple cream.
I've always heard that Brazilians take
like three two, three showers a day and
now I completely understand why they do
because it is so humid in Brazil. I'm
constantly sweating, so I've been taking
multiple showers a day like a true
Brazilian.
>> [music]
[music]
>> We're at this place called Solo cuz I've
heard so many good things about this
place. I just got a coffee and a
smoothie. It's like a mango, banana,
something smoothie. Yeah, cheers.
>> [music]
>> Oh my god. Oh my god.
That is
so good.
So, we're currently waiting on our Uber
cuz we're going to Santa Clara, which is
like a very popular mall here. It's like
12 stories.
Lena.
>> [music]
>> That is cute.
Oh, these are so cute.
Guys, I've never been to something like
this. A 12-story shopping mall. They
have the cutest shops in this mall. How
cute.
The way we're in a mall right now and
I'm still in my bikini top and no one
has batted an eye. Brazil is just
different. I love it here. I literally
love this content so much.
They're so cute.
Okay, so this is where you have to
customize. Oh my gosh, guys. What should
I get? They have cats.
Oh my gosh, so cute.
Copped it.
Got my coconut.
>> [music]
>> Cheers.
Cute.
>> [music]
>> The sunset is insane here. I know. Oh my
god. It looks like a painting. Cotton
candy
>> [music]
>> with
some something.
I really love steak. Steak is my
favorite food. You have barely seen me
on this vlog, but I have to tell you
that this bussin. Bussin. Brazilian
steak bussin. I'm trying chicken here
for the first time because a Brazilian
told me it's good. So, I'm trying to be
culturally
in there. Culturally
>> in there. In there.
Here it is.
It's kind of good. The consistency is
throwing me off a little though. Ashley,
I don't like it. I don't like it.
Market is not only from Rio, so we have
small [singing] stores from all over
Brazil. So, you can try a little bit of
food from the north, the south, from
[music] everywhere. We're looking real
rough, all of us. No, I'm glad we locked
it.
As a collective.
Who are you talking about? Guys, we
locked it in. We would have never
planned this. We'd be doing nothing
[clears throat] all day. Let's be
honest. No, you're
you're you're Let's just go see the
the Chrysler
Guys, I'm running on like 2 and 1/2
hours of sleep right now. We were out
last night and it was a late night. Now,
we're on a food tour.
With like no sleep. Vibes.
>> [music]
[singing]
[music]
>> Good? Good. Yeah?
Mhm. Pão de queijo. Pão de queijos are
out of this year.
Wow.
Açaí.
It's called açaí.
It's crazy.
I like the guava. All the food here is
so good.
Pão de queijo again. Cuz he's feeding me
stuff. Oh my Jesus Christ, he keeps
feeding me.
That's that's your love language. Yes,
he's cutting me through. Hello.
Yes, oh my god.
Stop. Didn't you say you
Nice to meet you. Nice to meet you.
I just met a subscriber in Brazil.
I'm here with the cheese bread, the
traditional cheese bread.
>> Pão de queijo. Yes.
That's that cheese bread and I love that
cheese bread. Like it's so good. You
can't take one until you say it right.
Pão de queijo.
So good.
I love Brazil.
You cannot be serious, bro.
Is that a shot in the morning? The shot,
espresso, and a a piece of bread. It's
not a shot, it's water.
Where are we? In Santa Teresa's
neighborhood. Santa Teresa.
We're in Santa Teresa.
Here we'll find the best pão de queijo
ever.
The best açaí I've ever had. They know
what they're doing. So, after the pão de
queijo, now we're headed to a bar here.
Apparently, they have the best
caipirinha here, which is a really
popular Brazilian drink. This is like a
caipirinha with no alcohol, so it's just
a juice. Caipirinha. And this is passion
fruit with lime.
>> [music]
>> Oh.
People here
Caipirinha.
It's very strong. Woah.
>> [music]
>> Guys, look how cute this cat is. It's
making me miss Pika and Leo so much.
He's such a good baby.
We're at a gas station right now. Sorry,
I can't even talk to you guys right now.
I'm so tired. We're headed to an island
to go on a boat.
That was underwhelming.
>> [music]
[music]
>> All righty, guys, we're about to get on
a boat.
Guys, Nina's over it.
She's tired.
>> [music]
>> We're here in the Blue Lagoon.
[music]
>> Guys, pray for us. They're they're
driving the boat right now. It's
intense.
>> [music]
>> All righty, vlog, we're getting off the
boat to eat. They pulled up with a boat
to the restaurant. There it is right
there. Guys, Brazilians are so nice.
They're a vibe.
Wow.
Those houses. Guys, I'm so hungry. It's
raining right now, but it's kind of a
vibe.
Guys, look how nice the view is at our
restaurant.
Georgina. This is my favorite view.
What is this called? Bacalhau. This is
bacalhau. Bacalhau.
Bacalhau. Bacalhau.
It's secure. Oh my god.
Wow. Oh my god, this is delicious.
Bacalhau.
Deliciouso.
I'm trying to do an aesthetic video,
guys, and Nina's like
This is called moqueca. Moqueca baiana.
I guess there will be no rain for the
next few days. [laughter]
>> [music]
>> Guys, this looks like Pika's brother.
He's such a cute cat. We made it to the
new Airbnb. Here she is. She's cute and
quaint. I mean, she does the job.
>> She does the job. She gets the job done.
>> Guys, guys, guys, no, let me tell you.
Let me tell you this. There are like no
hotels on this island, okay? There's
only like four Airbnbs max on this
island. Every single one of them was
like a one bedroom, and if there's more
than two beds, it's all in a shared huge
living room. No rooms. So, I booked the
nicest place possible.
Hello, guys. Editing Nina here. I just
wanted to come in here and say that
Airbnb was quite literally the worst
Airbnb I think I've ever stayed at. And
it wasn't my fault. It was just that
island. They only had hostels and just a
few Airbnbs, and obviously, an island is
not going to have the nicest Airbnbs.
But where we stayed, okay, there was
bugs on the bed. There was no hot water
and no towels. And so, my friends
literally had to use bedsheets as
towels. And it was just a huge
difference from the Airbnb we stayed at
in Rio. But still, it was an experience.
I'm editing it now, and I'm just
laughing cuz it was an experience that
honestly bonded all of us because it was
it was something. Okay, it was
something.
>> [music]
>> Damn, guys, we're really far from home.
We're really far from home. Guys, they
have the cutest stores on this island. I
won't say. They have like the cutest
jewelry. Sir, sir, how much how much is
this? Nina, you should get [music] one.
Woah, your beard is white. Is that
natural? No, no, that's natural. Oh, oh,
oh. That's the style.
>> I thought he's Brazilian style.
Oh,
is that cute? Oh my god.
>> [laughter]
>> I'm going crazy with the shopping on
this island. So, I'm getting this bikini
because I have the yellow one, and I'm
obsessed with it, so I'm getting it in
blue. Oh my god, this looks tiny. This
is a medium. This is not fitting me,
bro.
Um, maybe in child's medium?
Okay, let me get the correct size.
Currently here walking on a beach dead
at night. We are currently headed to
this party apparently that they have
here on this island. The way we had to
get here, I had to cross a river, and
I'm wearing sneakers right now. So, I
literally had to roll up my jeans and
then take off my sneakers and my socks
but leave them there. She did it for me
because she didn't want to leave me
alone cuz I really want to go to this
party cuz apparently, it's the best
after party on the whole island. We're
literally walking through a jungle right
now for this party. What hello?
>> [music]
[music]
>> We're literally walking through a jungle
right now to get to this beach.
I'm so excited. I'm fighting for my life
right now. Walking in this in flip-flops
not the move.
We made it to the beach.
Guys, this beach is insane. The sand
feels like corn starch, like so soft.
The sand is so soft.
This is definitely like top three
beaches I've ever been to in my life.
Guys, do you see this like little monkey
thing? Oh my gosh, she's right here.
Oh my gosh, she's eating the banana.
Oh my god. Oh my gosh, she got it.
I'm like looking around. It literally
does not even feel real that I'm here. I
think that this is my favorite country
to visit. The real ones know that I've
been talking about Brazil for years.
Like it has been on my bucket list for
years. Everything about this place is
just so I love it. I love it here. I
feel like it's because since I'm Korean
and I'm used to Korean culture,
Brazilian culture is just so different
from Korean culture in so many ways. And
so, it's like really cool to see [music]
how other people live. I just feel like
Brazilian culture is amazing. And
honestly, even though I've been like
filming everything on this trip, I have
been very mindful about being present.
Like having times in this trip where I'm
not using my phone at all. And when I
want to document stuff, obviously, I've
been using Cove. Me and my best friends
actually created a shared Cove on this
trip, and we've all been uploading our
photos and our moments, our videos. Our
shared Cove is filled with so many funny
photos, so many cute photos. Like I'm
literally obsessed with it. This trip
has by far been the best trip of my life
cuz I'm here with my best friends. I'm
in my favorite country, and
romanticizing it all on Cove has been
the reason why I feel like this trip is
just a 10 out of [music] 10, and I'm so
happy. I can't stop smiling. For being
in Brazil, I did not post as much as I
usually do, and that's because I've been
posting my moments onto Cove, because I
really wanted to be mindful and present
on this trip. At the end of the day,
that's what trips are about. It's not
about the Instagram photo, it's not
about the likes, it's not about showing
people that you're on this cool trip.
It's about being present, enjoying the
moment, living in the moment, [music]
and that is literally what Cove is
about. And now me and my best friends
get to remember this trip forever, and I
already want to come back to Brazil.
Guess who's here?
I've been trying to go to a beach for
the past [music] couple days.
I'm so happy to be on a beach right now.
Guys, she's such a beach island girl.
Like, I'm like more of a dip my foot in
the in the water. She's snorkeling,
she's in that water. Nah, the girl's
>> She's one with the ocean. Being in
nature makes me automatically smile. I
have not posted one thing on this whole
entire trip.
>> Are we in the Cove, though? We're in the
Cove.
>> [music]
>> I was telling them how usually on trips
like this, I post like I spam my
stories. I'm always getting photos and
videos. This trip, I've actually toned
it down a lot, and it's because of Cove.
Low-key though, I haven't been taking
any pictures or videos. But is that
okay?
>> You all know that the Cove in the air
drop later is going to be crazy. [music]
Exactly.
>> [music]
[music]
>> Oh, heads are taking a ride to join
[singing] us late.
>> [music]